http://homeopathyusa.org/aih-website-privacy-policy.html

State And Regional Societies
LMHI (International Assn of Medical Homeopaths)
Letter to FDA
AIH Accuses European Academies Science Advisory Council of Deliberate Scientific Bias
Patients
What is Homeopathic Medicine?
Regarding the Practice of Homeopathic Medicine
Find a Physician
Practitioners
In the News
AIH Accuses European Academies Science Advisory Council of Deliberate Scientific Bias
State And Regional Societies
LMHI (International Assn of Medical Homeopaths)
Letter to FDA
AIH Accuses European Academies Science Advisory Council of Deliberate Scientific Bias
Patients
What is Homeopathic Medicine?
Regarding the Practice of Homeopathic Medicine
Find a Physician
Practitioners
In the News
AIH Accuses European Academies Science Advisory Council of Deliberate Scientific Bias
AIH Website Privacy Policy
The American Institute of Homeopathy (AIH) supports the right of personal privacy and corporate security on the Internet. We will never sell or rent names, e-mail addresses or any other privileged information about our clients or subscribers.
HOW WE GATHER INFORMATION FROM USERS
Information may be used by our staff and our Website to complete the activity for which the information was provided, whether the activity is a one-time event, such as performing a service, forwarding an e-mail message or placing an order; or recurring events, such as events, notices or a message series.
How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase.
You may provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive areas of our site. Like most Web sites, our site collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors.
For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site.
As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customize the site's features according to your preferences.
WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT
Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content. We respect your privacy and do not share your information with anyone.
Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive).
Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you individually.
We may use personally Identifiable information collected on our site to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by us and other topics we think you might find of interest.
Personally Identifiable Information collected by us may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions, administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example) may access such information. We will use your information only as permitted by law.
In addition, we may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.
ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION
The AIH, entities for whom it is acting as an agent, and/or entities acting as its agent, may be provided information you supplied in order to perform a service or action you requested. An agent for these purposes is defined as a third party that utilizes data only for the completion of the stated purpose, such as an order fulfillment service.
We strive to offer our visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. We will never sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party. Period.
CHANGES TO THIS POLICY
AIH reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.
Support Our Work — Make a Donation!
To make a donation to the American Institute of Homeopathy (AIH), please visit our donation page.
American Institute of Homeopathyc/o Mitchell A. Fleisher, MD, DHt, DABFM, Trustee10190 Critzers Shop RoadAfton, Virginia 22920
You are here: AIH Website Privacy Policy      ^ Top
Search:
Home | About Us | Privacy Policy | Contact Us
Copyright © 2007-2016, American Institute of Homeopathy. All rights reserved.
The material contained in this website is for informational purposes only and no assumptions should be made regarding its accuracy. Any information provided here and any recommendations made should not be used to, nor are intended to, diagnose, treat cure or mitigate any specific health problem. Anybody with any health complaints should seek the care and consultation of an appropriately licensed health care practitioner. No attempt should be made to use any information provided here as a form of treatment for any specific condition without approval and guidance of a physician.The American Institute of Homeopathy, or any person involved in the production or management of this website, is not responsible for the use of, or the result of the use of, the information contained in this website.
